<SBPquiz>

<question>
<q>
Which one of the following measures should the next student body president take to enhance safety on campus? 
</q>
<a can="m">
Institute a self-defense training program for first-year students as a part of Week of Welcome and add first-aid training to the LFIT curriculum.
</a>
<a can="r">
Publicize the right for assault victims to use campus safe rooms or to file an anonymous blind report.
</a>
<a can="i">
Adopt a policy of alcohol medical amnesty for alcohol-related health emergencies.
</a>
<a can="b">
Work with the Department of Public Safety and Chapel Hill Police Department to become more transparent about expectations, especially for events like Halloween. 
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
How would you like the next student body president to advocate on behalf of students for tuition? 
</q>
<a can="b">
Create a tuition report available on Connect Carolina that shows exactly where tuition costs are going.
</a>
<a can="m">
Focus on the Carolina Advocacy Committee and lobbying to state legislators in Raleigh.
</a>
<a can="i">
Form a study that analyzes the cost of an undergraduate education, and push for a new cost-based tuition plan that sets tuition rates based on the findings of this study.
</a>
<a can="r">
Prepare a "worst case scenario document" at the end of the year to keep students and parents abreast about likely tuition realities.
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
What new service would you most like the University to provide?
</q>
<a can="i">
Free ActiTV ads for student organizations, which is a display space on the student union display screens near Alpine, which currently cost $25 a week.
</a>
<a can="r">
Student government assistance for writing grants related to the arts. 
</a>
<a can="b">
More late night and weekend hours at dining halls.
</a>
<a can="m">
Express housing checkout, which would allow students to check out of their dorm room at the end of the year without having to schedule a meeting with an RA.
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
How would you like to see environmental affairs improve at UNC? 
</q>
<a can="m">
Create a program called "EcoHarmony" that acts as an online resource for students to search for environmental groups to join and host at least two environmental roundtables per year to facilitate discussion among campus leaders.
</a>
<a can="i">
Work with housing to make dorms more like Morrison, which just won a national EPA competition for energy savings. 
</a>
<a can="r">
Keep UNC accountable on its energy policies. For example, pushing for a responsible shift from coal to biomass and maintaining pressure on University coal coming from surface mines. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Limit paper usage in classrooms by encouraging professors to use Turnitin.com, which allows for paperless grading while maintaining academic integrity in an online world.
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
How would you like to see academic affairs improve?
</q>
<a can="b">
Create an instant messaging tool that allows students to ask urgent or short questions to an academic advisor, similar to the system for UNC libraries. 
</a>
<a can="i">
Make online course syllabi available during registration. 
</a>
<a can="r">
Restructure the undergraduate bulletin so it provides more specific course overviews and makes course planning easier and more user-friendly.
</a>
<a can="m">
Improve the logistics for faculty to teach in departments other than their own. 
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
Which would you most likely participate in to help promote diversity on campus?
</q>
<a can="i">
Push the administration to partner with other institutions, like North Carolina Central University, to build relationships between diverse communities.
</a>
<a can="m">
Work to establish a Latino center on campus according to the Carolina Latina/o Collaborative's determined deadlines.
</a>
<a can="r">
Host a multi-cultural celebration similar to Fall Fest at the beginning of the year for first-year students. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Help set future goals and frameworks for the diversity of UNC, based on an assessment the Division of Student Affairs will be conducting. 
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
How should the next student body president work with Carolina athletics? 
</q>
<a can="r">
In exchange for submitting a great idea on how to make campus better, the next president will offer up his or her basketball ticket as part of an incentive system to improve our campus. 
</a>
<a can="i">
It doesn't matter to me if the next student body president works with Carolina athletics. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Make athletic events more green by having more recycling bins at Kenan Stadium and the Dean Dome. 
</a>
<a can="m">
Create a listserv to remind students when to sign up for the basketball ticket lottery. 
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
What would you like to see happen within student government? 
</q>
<a can="i">
Have committees serve as knowledge centers for issues on campus rather than acting as individual, mini-student organizations. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Create a committee of graduate students within the student government cabinet so that their voices will be heard. 
</a>
<a can="m">
Spend less time working on projects that other student groups are better equipped to do.
</a>
<a can="r">
Improve relationships between student congress and the executive branch.
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
How can the next student body president help out student organizations? 
</q>
<a can="m">
Introduce the college social networking site, Collegiate Link, to help connect students to organizations on campus. 
</a>
<a can="r">
Form communities of like-minded organizations in order to increase collaboration and efficiency between groups. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Create a map of all the organizations at Fall Fest, and strategically organize booths by type of organization. 
</a>
<a can="i">
Create a Presidential Leadership Council comprised of the presidents of 30 large student organizations. 
</a>
</question>

<question>
<q>
If the student body president could accomplish one new thing while in office, what would you want it be? 
</q>
<a can="i">
Improve parking issues with carpool parking permits, half-off parking tickets if paid in seven days, and free Rams deck parking after 5 p.m. 
</a>
<a can="b">
Create and post a "Carolina Calendar" of all the events from different student organizations, Carolina Athletics, Global Education Center, Sonja Haynes Stone Center and Memorial Hall.
</a>
<a can="r">
Reform the current system of student fees, targeting specific ones that should be reduced, increased or completely abolished.
</a>
<a can="m">
Establish a Student Enrichment Fund that students can apply to in order to attend conferences, seminars or lectures.
</a>
</question>

<candidate name="Mary Cooper" btn="mary_btn" link="http://www.mary4sbp.org/" pic="mary.jpg">
<bio>Mary Cooper is an environmental health science major and chemistry minor from Nashville, Tenn. She is the co-chairwoman for HOPE gardens and an active member on the Chancellor's Innovation Team and the Energy Task force. She has also served as co-chairwoman for the Environmental Affairs Committee.
</bio>
<point>Institute a self-defense training program for first year students as a part of Week of Welcome and add a first-aid training to the LFIT curriculum.
</point>
<point>Focus on the Carolina Advocacy Committee and lobbying to state legislators in Raleigh.
</point>
<point>Institute express housing checkout, which would allow students to check out of their dorm room at the end of the year without having to schedule a meeting with an RA.
</point>
<point>Create a program called "EcoHarmony" that acts as on online resource for students to search for environmental groups to join and host at least two environmental roundtables per year to facilitate discussion among campus leaders.
</point>
<point>Improve the logistics for faculty to teach in departments other than their own.
</point>
<point>Work to establish a Latino center on campus according to the Carolina Latina/o Collaborative's determined deadlines.
</point>
<point>Create a listserv to remind students when to sign up for the basketball ticket lottery.
</point>
<point>Spend less time working on projects that other student groups are better equipped to do.
</point>
<point>Introduce the college social networking site, Collegiate Link, to help connect students to organizations.
</point>
<point>Establish a Student Enrichment Fund that students can apply to in order to attend conferences, seminars or lectures.
</point>
</candidate>

<candidate name="Rick Ingram" btn="rick_btn" link="http://flywebdesigns.net/rick4sbp/" pic="rick.jpg">
<bio>Rick Ingram is a political science and economics major from Asheville, N.C.  Ingram has been involved with student government and Young Democrats while at UNC.
</bio>
<point>Publicize the right for assault victims to use campus safe rooms or to file an anonymous blind report.
</point>
<point>Prepare a "worst case scenario document" at the end of the year to keep students and parents abreast about likely tuition realities.
</point>
<point>Student government assistance for writing grants related to the arts. 
</point>
<point>Keep UNC accountable on its energy policies. For example, pushing for a responsible shift from coal to biomass and maintaining pressure on University coal coming from surface mines.
</point>
<point>Restructure the undergraduate bulletin so it provides more specific course overviews and makes course planning easier and more user-friendly. 
</point>
<point>Host a multi-cultural celebration similar to Fall Fest at the beginning of the year for first year students.
</point>
<point>In exchange for submitting a great idea on how to make campus better, the next president will offer up his or her basketball ticket as a part of an incentive system to improve our campus.
</point>
<point>Improve relationships between student congress and the executive branch.
</point>
<point>Form communities of like-minded organizations in order to increase collaboration and efficiency between groups.
</point>
<point>Reform the current system of student fees, targeting specific ones that should be reduced, increased or completely abolished.
</point>
</candidate>

<candidate name="Ian Lee" btn="ian_btn" link="http://www.carolinaspark.org/Ian4SBP/Home.html" pic="ian.jpg">
<bio>Ian Lee is a business major from Cary, N.C. He is also the current student body secretary. He has been involved with Model UN, the General Alumni Association, Campus Y, the Daily Tar Heel, and Innovation@Carolina. 
</bio>
<point>Adopt a policy of alcohol medical amnesty for alcohol-related health emergencies.
</point>
<point>Form a study that analyzes the cost of an undergraduate education, and push for a new cost-based tuition plan that sets tuition rates based on the findings of this study.
</point>
<point>Free ActiTV ads for student organizations, which is a display space on the student union display screens near Alpine that cost $25 a week.
</point>
<point>Work with housing to make dorms more like Morrison, which just won a national EPA competition for energy savings.
</point>
<point>Make online course syllabi available during registration.
</point>
<point>Push the administration to partner with other institutions, like North Carolina Central University, to build relationships between diverse communities.
</point>
<point>Ian Lee doesn't have a platform point that focuses on athletics. 
</point>
<point>Rather than committees acting as individual mini-student organizations, they should serve as knowledge centers for issues on campus.
</point>
<point>Create a single funding application for student organizations that will go to a team of advisors.
</point>
<point>Improve parking issues with carpool parking permits, half-off parking tickets if paid in seven days, and free Rams deck parking after 5 p.m.
</point>
</candidate>

<candidate name="Brooklyn Stephens" btn="brooklyn_btn" link="http://brooklynforsbp.weebly.com/" pic="brooklyn.jpg">
<bio>Brooklyn Stephens is a psychology and sociology major from Wake Forest, N.C. She has been an orientation leader and served as a Resident Advisor for two years. She has been involved with the UNC Dance Marathon as a dancer, a committee member and now as a campus fundraising sub-chair. She is also involved with Campus Crusade for Christ.  
</bio>
<point>Work with the Department of Public Safety and Chapel Hill Police Department to become more transparent about expectations, especially for events like Halloween.
</point>
<point>Create a tuition report available on Connect Carolina that shows exactly where tuition costs are going. 
</point>
<point>More late night and weekend hours at dining halls.
</point>
<point>Limit paper usage in classrooms by encouraging professors to use Turnitin.com, which allows for paperless grading while maintaining academic integrity in an online world.
</point>
<point>Create an instant messaging tool that allows students to ask urgent or short questions to an academic advisor, similar to the system used by UNC libraries. 
</point>
<point>Help set future goals and frameworks for the diversity of UNC based on an assessment the Division of Student Affairs will be conducting.
</point>
<point>Make athletic events more green by having more recycling bins at Kenan Stadium and the Dean Dome.
</point>
<point>Create a committee of graduate students within the student government cabinet so that their voices will be heard.
</point>
<point>Create a map of all the organizations at Fall Fest, and strategically organize booths by type of organization.
</point>
<point>Create and post a "Carolina Calendar" of all the events from different student organizations, Carolina Athletics, Global Education Center, Sonja Haynes Stone Center and Memorial Hall.
</point>
</candidate>

</SBPquiz>
